Happy New Year!
We are the Hidari Expedition!
January 2, 2023, which means the first sale of Libbins
Mr. Hidari Northeast and Weird Uncle
It's an island, it's an island
It's an island, it's an island!
Today now, I'm going to announce to the three of you that we're coming to Kanrai.
We've done this before, haven't we?
We're going to have you do the first sale version of it.
On such a happy day
I'm so happy!
Please be less goofy today.
I hear there's a lot of great people here.
But it's so nice to be pissed off
Argh.
So I'm going to move to the first floor now and do some informations.
Let's go.
Okay, we're here.
Here we are.
Good morning.
A little higher on the right.
Top right? Too far up?
And again.
This is the beginner's store.
You guys sell the oily noodles on the fourth floor.
Chisso's.
Please make sure you deliver this to me.
Yes, I'll read it to you.
Don't force yourself to use honorifics.
I'll speak.
You don't have to say it.
Don't forget to cut the cans.
Beef tongue!
I'm going.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much for coming to E-Bee's first sale today.
I'm Hazuki-Una from Inari and Hokusan.
Yes, yes.
I'd like to inform our customers who are visiting our store.
We are currently holding a special event at the Mori no Garden Terrace on the 4th floor.
We are offering a special first sale price of 100 yen including tax
We are offering a special New Year's sale price of 100 yen including tax!
The offer will end as soon as it is gone.
Please come to the Garden Terrace on the 4th floor.
Thank you very much for visiting us today!
Thank you for watching!
Ok, I couldn't be that funny, so I can just say that I'm reading the script correctly and that's the way I usually speak.
Like a person who is tired from all the boo-boo's and obi's.
The point of being an idiot with a boo-boo or an obi is to live in San's case.
He's very responsive.
Last time we had a light on the president, he announced that the money was coming from the president.
Oh, my God, the president said that.
Nell, let's go.
Let's go. - Hello.
Thank you for coming to Eby's for our first sale.
Thank you very much.
I would like to inform you of an event during your visit.
Oh, wow!
We are now holding a New Year's lucky draw at the Garden Terrace on the 4th floor.
Try your luck in the New Year!
Sorry, sir.
We are holding a New Year's lottery to try your luck!
Please bring in a receipt of 3,000 yen or more to participate in the event.
Please try it out!
I can't believe I'm reading that right.
Please come to the 4th Floor Forest Garden Terrace!
Thank you very much for visiting us today!
This is Mio Fujitani!
Thank you for watching!
Oh!
What the hell?
I think there's something wrong with the microphone.
I'm not very good at putting on a pitch.
I did it.
What was the first time? You were smoking snakes? You were smoking it? Just now.
I was smoking.
You can smoke it from here.
Oh!
What's the New Year's Plum Trial?
I made a mistake.
Plum candy?
New Year Plum Tasting.
I made a mistake.
It's like a plum orchid test, isn't it?
It was in a child's voice...
In an adult's voice.
Thank you very much.
Like a child made a mistake.
If it's done in a goofy way...
Yes, that's true.
It's difficult.
Yes, it is.
Well, then, by golly...
Bird.
Rabbit's onlyJust a Rabbit's Claw
Because last time we sang.
I sang it.
Here we go!
Thank you very much for coming to Eby's New Year's Sale today!
I would like to give a brief introduction to our guests.
We are now on the 4th floor.
At the 4th floor, in the special exhibition hall, there is a rabbit named after this year's Eto.
The bunny rabbit, Usa-chan, is waiting for you all with great anticipation.
Please come with a cute heart while thinking about the bunny rabbit's feelings.
Thank you very much for coming today.
Laughter
Riddle!
Piglet at the end
I felt like I was in a fantasy.
Pi-Pon, it was Disney, wasn't it?
Pi-Pin I wanted to meet Uso-chan, didn't I?
Yes, Uso-chan, yes...
Pi-chan Is she the one who deals with the rabbits?
Pi-chan Are you on the rabbit side?
I didn't know which side he was on.
Laughter
Ping Ping Ping, you're so lively.
Did it say anything about thinking about the rabbit's feelings?
P Pion No, it didn't say that.
Pyon No. Original? It was really good, wasn't it?
Pyon: It was totally good.
It was super good!
It was good.
I can be a breeder.
I've never heard of a rabbit breeder.
New Year's announcement of cold and warm weather
PYON I want to make lots of announcements this year
PYON I want to do it!
PYON You love this series, don't you?
P P P P P P P P P Next time, when there aren't so many big people around.
PYON Yes, that's why.
P P P I want to do it when no one's around.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.